Guide to the Eric M. and Carol L. Meyers papers, 1970-2019 UA.29.02.0027
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Eric M. and Carol L. Meyers papers
1970-2019
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Meyers, Carol L.
Meyers, Eric M.
UA.29.02.0027
60.0 Linear Feet 53 boxes; 9 oversize folders
7 Gigabytes 1296 files
Eric M. and Carol L. Meyers are professors in Duke University's Department of Religion. Throughout their careers, they have conducted archeological digs in relation to their interest in biblical and Judaic studies. The collection contains extensive materials related to several major excavations the pair conducted in Israel from the 1970s to the 1990s. The materials in the collection include binders and notebooks of field notes, charts, maps, and records; notecards; photographs (including slides, prints, and negatives), almost all black-and-white; a few audiovisual items; clippings; some administrative and correspondence files; coins; and drawings of sites and artifacts. There are many electronic files, some of which represent items not present in the collection. Topics include 20th century archaeology and practices; the Sepphoris, Meiron, Khirbet Shema, Nabratein, and Gush Halav excavation sites in Israel, including maps and photographs of the sites; Jewish and Arabic artifacts such as coins and pottery; other ancient artifacts; and religious and biblical studies as they relate to archaeology.
Biographical Note
Eric M. and Carol L. Meyers are both professors in the Department of Religion at Duke University.
Eric M. Meyers joined Duke in 1969, after receiving his Ph.D. from Harvard University. Since joining the faculty of Duke, Eric Meyers has published extensively in the fields of biblical archeology and Judaism, often collaborating with wife Carol Meyers. He has also directed many archeological excavations in Israel and Italy. Eric Meyers is now Bernice and Morton Lerner Professor of Judaic Studies, and directs the Graduate Program in Religion.
Carol L. Meyers received her Ph.D. from Brandeis University, and joined Duke in 1977. Like her husband, Carol Meyers also focuses on biblical archeology and biblical studies, and is especially interested in the role of women in the biblical world. She has published widely, and directs many archeological excavations. She is Co-Director of Duke's Summer in Israel Program, and also directs undergraduate studies in the Duke Department of Religion. The holder of the Mary Grace Wilson Professorship in Religion, Carol Meyers is also an affiated faculty member in the Women Studies Program at Duke.
Conditions Governing Access
Electronic records have been migrated to a library server and digital use copies can only be accessed onsite in the Rubenstein Library reading room. To request access, please contact the Rubenstein Library before coming to use these records.
Access Restrictions
The list of contents was provided by the donor and contents have not been processed.
Original audiovisual materials are closed to use; copies must be made for access. Also, film negatives are closed to use; prints and electronic scans of these images may exist in the collection.
Provenance
The Eric M. and Carol L. Meyers Papers were received by the University Archives as a gift in 1982; 1988; 1994; 2003; 2010; 2017; and 2019.
Collection Overview
The collection contains extensive materials related to several major excavations conducted by the Meyers and their teams in Israel from the 1970s to the 1990s, as well as materials related to later publications about their work. Formats include binders and notebooks of field notes, charts, and records; maps; notecards; photographs (including many slides, prints, and negatives); coins; news clippings; a few video and audio recordings; some administrative and correspondence files; and many drawings of sites and artifacts. There are also electronic records, most of which are black-and-white scans of photographs, negatives, and field notebooks, and drawings, many of these, but not all, are scans of items located in the collection.
Topics represented by the materials include 20th century archaeology and practices; the Sepphoris, Meiron, Khirbet Shema, Nabratein, and Gush Halav excavation sites in Israel, including maps and many photographs of the sites; Jewish and Arabic artifacts such as coins and pottery; other ancient artifacts; and religious and biblical studies as they relate to archaeology.
Materials have been kept in the binders and folders in which they were received. The collection is organized by accession number, but materials in separate accession number groups are intrinsically connected.
The addition (A2003-30) includes binders from an archeological dig in Gush Halav, and Arabic and Jewish coins from the Meiron and Khirbet Shema digs.
Accessions from 2010 and 2017 include materials from archeological digs in Nabratein, Meiron, Gush Halav, and Khirbet Shema.
The accessions from 2019 include materials from digs in Khirbet Shema, Gush Halav, Nabratein, Meiron, and Sepphoris, among other materials. Also received in 2019 are over 1200 digital files from the Sepphoris site, which have been migrated to a library server.
Archaeologists -- United States; Archaeology; Archaeology and religion; Bible -- Study and teaching; Coins, Arab; Coins, Jewish; Excavations (Archaeology); Excavations (Archaeology) -- Israel -- Meron; Jews -- Antiquities; Pottery, Israeli; Gush Halav Site (Israel); Israel -- Antiquities; Meron (Israel) -- Antiquities; Nabratein Site (Israel); Sepphoris (Extinct city); Shema Site (Israel); Audiovisual materials; Coins; Electronic records; Maps; Negatives (photographs); Photographs; Slides (photographs); Meyers, Carol L.; Duke University. Department of Religion; Meyers, Eric M.
- Accession Number 82-72
  Scope and Contents note
  These materials contain information about the Meyerses' digs in Meiron and Khirbet Shema in Israel during the early and mid-1970s. These notes and records were later used as sources for two books co-written by the Meyerses, Excavations at Ancient Meiron, Upper Galilee, Israel 1971-72, 1974-75, 1977, and Ancient Synagogue Excavations at Khirbet Shema, Upper Galilee, Israel 1970-1972. The letters and numbers used to identify the various binders and folders (i.e. MV 4) indicate a particular physical part of the excavation site. Only some of the binders and folders are dated.
  - MV 1, 2, 3, 4 (Box 1)
  - MV 4 (Box 1)
  - MBI 1, 3 (Box 1)
  - MBI 2 (Box 1)
  - MV 5, 1975 (Box 1)
  - MVI (Box 1)
  - MVII 3 (Box 1)
  - MVII 2, 1977 (Box 1)
  - MVII 1, 1977 (Box 1)
  - C-6 (MI 3) and C-7 (MVII 1), 1975-1977 (Box 1)
  - MI 2, 1975 (Box 2)
  - MII 4, 1977 (Box 2)
  - MIV 2, 1974 (Box 2)
  - C-1 (MIII 4) and C-2, 1972-1974 (Box 2)
  - MII 3, 1977 (Box 2)
  - MII 5 (Box 2)
  - MI 3, 1975 (Box 2)
  - MI 4 (Box 2)
  - MIII 3, 6, 7 (Box 2)
  - MIII 4, 5 (Box 2)
  - Photos, M, 2", 1974 (Box 3)
  - M, B&W [photos], 1975 (Box 3)
  - M, 35mm photos, 1972-1974 (Box 3)
  - MIII, 1, 2 (Box 3)
  - MI 5 (Box 4)
  - MI 6 (Box 4)
  - MI 1, 3 (Box 4)
  - MI 2 (Box 4)
  - MI 2, 8 (Box 4)
  - MI 7, 8 (Box 4)
  - MI 1, 2, 1972 (Box 4)
  - Field notebooks for Khirbet Shema excavation, 1970-1972 (Box 5)
  - Field notebooks for Khirbet Shema excavation, 1970-1972 (Box 6)
  - [Khirbet Shema Weekly Reports], 1971 (Box 7)
  - Meiron Weekly Reports, 1977 (Box 7)
  - Meiron Weekly Reports, 1972 (Box 7)
  - Meiron Pottery Readings and Critical Locus List, 1974 (Box 7)
  - [Khibet Shema Weekly Reports (4 binders)], 1970-1971 (Box 7)
  - Khibet Shema Registry, 1970-1971 (Box 7)
- Accession number A88-0040
  These 6.5" x 9" registry cards were produced to document artifacts found at the Khirbet Shema and Meiron archeological sites in Israel in the 1970s. Some of the cards feature pencil drawings of the objects.
  - Registry cards for artifacts from Khirbet Shema and Meiron sites, 1970-1977 (Box 7)
- Accession number A94-116
  These field notebooks from the Khirbet Shema excavation in Israel date from 1971. The letters and numbers used to identify the notebooks indicate specific physical places at the excavation site.
  - NW VII.27, 1971 (Box 7)
  - SE II.8[15], 1971 (Box 7)
  - SE II.1[7-8], 1971 (Box 7)
  - SE II.7[14], 1971 (Box 7)
- Accession number A2003-30
  - Gush Halav binders (Box 8)
    - I.1, 1977-1978 (Box 8)
    - I.2, 1978 (Box 8)
    - I.3, 1977 (Box 8)
    - I.4, 1977-1978 (Box 8)
    - I.5, 1977 (Box 8)
    - I.6, 1978 (Box 8)
  - Khirbet Shema coin samples, 1970-1974 (Box 9)
  - Meiron coin samples, 1977 (Box 10)
  - Khirbet Shema coin samples, 1970-1975 (Box 10)
  - Photo File, Coin Negatives, 1977 (Box 11)
  - Transcript of Conference with Ya'akov Meshorer on Meiron, 1980 (Box 11)
  - Tyrian Influence in the Upper Galilee, by Richard S. Hanson, 1980 (Box 11)
  - Khirbet Shema coin samples, 1971-1974 (Box 11)
  - Meiron coin samples, 1977 (Box 11)
  - Khirbet Shema Arabic coin samples, 1970-1971 (Box 11)
- Accession UA2010.0011, 5
  - Old Correspondence: Summer Program [from students] (Box 25)
  - Summer Program 1974 (and 73 - HOC), 1973-1974 (Box 25)
  - MEP: Meiron - Publication Materials, IAA (IDA) records (Box 25)
  - Photos - Meiron - Objects (Box 25)
  - Meiron - Photos/ Prints (Box 25)
  - Appendix D [possibly C): Foodstuffs Lr/Shultz Wiesel (Box 25)
  - MI Materials (Box 25)
  - N80 N81 Group Photos (Box 25)
  - NAB Press Releases, 1980 (Box 25)
  - NAB 81 (ark), Clippings, Press, Letters, etc (Box 25)
  - Gush Halav - Publication matters and IAA documents (Box 25)
  - Group Photos M/GH 77 and GH 78, 1977-1978 (Box 25)
  - Pottery Readings GH 77, 78, 1977-1978 (Box 25)
  - Gush Halav 77/78 Coin Readings (Box 25)
  - [unlabeled pouch of photos and documents, possibly 'GH' related] (Box 25)
  - GH 77 /78 Working Drawings of architectural frags, reconstructions (Box 25)
  - Working Drawings for stratigraphic analysis GH 77/78 (Box 25)
  - Unlabled, GH related images / drawings (Box 25)
  - Gush Halav - negatives, photos of drawings (Box 25)
  - Figures [possibly Gush Halav] (Box 25)
  - Drawings (Box 25)
  - Gush Halav plates of various objects, metal items and lamps, 8 items (Box 25)
  - Gush Halav pottery plates, 32 items (Box 25)
  - Meiron Book- chs. I, II and III, extra prints of figures/drawings (Box 26)
  - Carol Asamec, stone obj? (Box 26)
  - Photos - Meiron - Field Shots (Box 26)
  - Meiron Baulk Drawings (Box 26)
  - Meiron arch frags to be inked (Box 26)
  - Meiron - MII4 - Passover Rm an F (and RM C), objects potter [photographs] Folder: Khirbat Shema, photos, etc (Box 26)
  - Supervisor's Manual Kh. Shema, '72, 1972 (Box 26)
  - Work Drawings [Meiron?] (Box 26)
  - C-2 Negatives pottery (Box 26)
  - Meiron volume, chs IV, V, VI, VII, VIII, IX, X, extra copies of figs (drawings) 5 folders Meiron Negatives (Box 26)
  - Unpublished drawings from Meiron (Box 26)
  - Loose drawings (Box 26)
  - Pictures and drawings (Box 26)
  - Pack of Meiron "pottery description sheets" with drawings (Box 26)
  - Meiron Pottery and object plates, 15 items (Box 26)
  - Meiron negatives (Box 26)
  - Negatives or transparency sheets(?) labeled with chapter numbers, ex "chpt 4", 5 items (Box 26)
  - Drawings Kh. Shema (Box 26)
  - Slides extra slides and negative strips - Meiron most likely (Box 26)
  - "Ml 1" "MI 4" "MI 5" and "MI 6" containing drawings, 4 folders (Box 26)
  - Transparencies and Xeroxed images of objects, 2 folders (Box 26)
  - Boo:, Ancient Synagogue Excavations at Khirbet Shema ', Upper Galilee, Israel 1970-1972 (Box 27)
  - Slide book/binder: "Master Slide collection" Khirbet Shema' 1970-1971, includes Table of contents for slide books 1 - 4. This appears to be book 1 (Box 27)
  - Slide books/binders: Khribet Shema Slides vols. II - IV (see book l for table of contents for these books), 3 Volumes (Box 27)
  - Book: Meiron Excavation Project, Volume V, Excavations at the Ancient Synagogue of Gush Halav (Box 28)
  - Book: Meiron Excavation Project, Volume VI, Excavations at Ancient Nabrathein: Synagogue and Environs (Box 28)
  - Slide book/binder: Meiron, Mil, MIii (synagogue), MV, MVI, MVII Objects (Box 28)
  - Binder: Meiron Book, Illustrations, plates (key to plates), drawings (Box 28)
  - Binder of photographs and negatives: Meiron/GH 1977 B/W (Box 28)
  - Small books of photography logs predominantly from Meiron and Gush Halav 77-78 and undated. One book includes material from KS 1972., 9 Gigabytes (Box 29)
  - Slide book/binder: Gush Halav (Box 29)
  - Gush Halav photographs and negatives ( one binder dated 1978), 2 Volumes (Box 29)
  - Book: Excavations at Ancient Meiron, Upper Galilee, Israel 1971-72, 1974-75, 1977 (Box 29)
- Accession UA2010.0034, 6
  - Nabratein Papers, binders labeld 1.1-1.7, circa 1980, 7 Volumes (Box 12)
  - Binder: "NAB 80, 81" Nabratein papers and slides (Box 13)
  - Nabratein Papers, some binders labeled: II.I, III. 1-4, IV. 1-3, 6 Volumes (Box 13)
  - Video tape: Finding Nabratein (Box 14)
  - Black and white images Nabratein, 4 Volumes (Box 14)
  - Binder: "Final reports, N80, N81" (Box 14)
  - Khirbet Shema '71, vols. 1-111, photographs and negatives, 3 Volumes (Box 15)
  - Binder: Khribet Shema '72, negatives and proof sheets (Box 15)
  - Binder: Khirbet Sberna '70, photographs (Box 16)
  - Khirbet Shema '72, negatives and photographs, 2 Volumes (Box 16)
  - Khirbet Shema, negatives and drawings, 2 Volumes (Box 16)
  - Binder: Meiron papers (Box 16)
  - Khirbet Shema negatives and drawing from Khribet Sberna and Meiron (Box 17)
  - Drawings and Pictures from unknown excavation (Box 18)
  - Nabratein drawings, photographs and papers (Box 19)
  - Nabratein drawings, photographs and papers (Box 20)
  - Nabratein drawings, photographs and papers (Box 21)
  - Gush Halav papers, slides and drawings. Meiron photographs. (Box 22)
  - Meiron slides, photographs, papers and drawings (Box 23)
  - Nabratein pottery descriptions by plate number, Khirbet Shema slides (Box 24)
  - Meiron drawings (Oversize-folder 1)
  - Meiron drawings (Oversize-folder 2)
  - Meiron drawings (Oversize-folder 3)
  - Nabratein drawings (Oversize-folder 4)
  - Drawings from unknown excavation (Oversize-folder 5)
- Accession UA2017.0065
  - News clippings: Khirbet Shema (Box 26)
  - News clippings: Meiron (Box 26)
- Accession UA2019.0028, 7 Gigabytes 1296 files (.jpg, .exif, .tif, .pdf, .doc, OLE2)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Electronic records in this series have been migrated to a library server and digital use copies can only be accessed onsite in the Rubenstein Library reading room. To request access, please contact the Rubenstein Library before coming to use these records.
  Scope and Contents
  Series comprises eletronic files of scanned photographic images, fieldbooks, and illustrations, all relating to the archaeological work on the Sepphoris site in Israel by teams from Duke University, led by Carol and Eric Meyers, and Hebrew University. The majority of the scans represent physical objects found in the Meyers collection.
  Series dates for electronic files indicate the creation date for the digital scans rather than the physical objects or images. Series descriptions were taken almost verbatim from donor-supplied notes received with the electronic files.
  The photographic images, most of which are scans of physical prints and negatives in the Meyers collection, were taken by Sepphoris site team members from about 1984 to 1995, almost all in black-and-white. Most are of site excavations and objects found in situ; another much smaller group consists of Sepphoris artifacts photographed in the U.S. lab in 2011. The fieldbooks date from 1984 to 1997 and contain extensive notes as well as some photographs; this group also includes the 2000 Duke team final site reports in .pdf format. Many of the original field notebooks are in the collection at Hebrew University, thus the scans may be the only representation in the Meyers papers. The Sepphoris illustration archive contains scans of drawings and other work, some of which were used for the 2013 Duke publication on Sepphoris pottery.
  - Sepphoris Illustrations Archive, 2009-2015; 3 Gigabytes 669 files (369 .tif, 292 .jpg, 5 OLE2, 2 .pdf, 1 MS Word .doc)
    Series contains scans of primarily ink drawings of artifacts excavated by the Duke team over the years. The scans should correlate with the data in the electronic spreadsheet file, also available in this series. The four main sub-folders are: 2011 and 2012 (from Yulia Rudman); Duke Drawings Archive; Hebrew U Archive Pottery Scans; and Studio Shots of Artifacts.
    - 2011 and 2012 (from Yulia Rudman) (Digital-materials UA.29.02.0027-SET-0001)
      These are primarily ceramic artifacts that were set aside for drawing after the 2011 dig and a study season following that dig. Yulia Rudman is the Jerusalem-based artist who created them for the publication project team. The drawings were done digitally.
    - Duke drawings archive (Digital-materials UA.29.02.0027-SET-0001)
      These are scans of ink drawings stored in sleeves in large white binders in the Meyers papers. File names are meant to correspond with the labels on the sleeves.
    - Hebrew University Archive pottery scans (Digital-materials UA.29.02.0027-SET-0001)
      These scans were done in Jerusalem, as the inkings themselves are located there. A note to provide some context and background: The Hebrew University and Duke teams split around 1990, and at that point divided up the archaeological site they had been excavating into two fields: a Hebrew U field and a Duke field. The "Hebrew U Archive Pottery Scans" contains pottery drawings from both fields. Those that are under the proprietary domain of Hebrew U consist of any drawing with a registration number beginning with 84.3, 85.2, 86.1, 86.2, 86.3. (Those numbers are the excavation areas within the Hebrew U field.) These drawings are not included on the spreadsheet "Artifact Drawings and Photos Archive," because they were not used in the Duke publication project.
    - Studio shots of artifacts (Digital-materials UA.29.02.0027-SET-0001)
      While most of the black-and-white photo archive consists of field photos, there are a several contact sheets with artifact photos. They are included in this sub-folder.
  - Field Photographs, 2005-2015; 2 Gigabytes 490 files (464 .jpg, 14 .exif, 12 OLE2) (Digital-materials UA.29.02.0027-SET-0001)
    Series contains scans of most but not all field photographs located in the black-and-white photographic archive, taken at the Sepphoris site in Israel between 1984 and 1995. Sub-folders, referenced by three digits representing the year and the site, represent eight different excavation areas. The color photographs in the Meyers papers are only available in slide form (transparencies) and have never been scanned.
  - Fieldbooks, 2011-2019; 2 Gigabytes 42 files (.pdf) (Digital-materials UA.29.02.0027-SET-0001)
    These are scans of the fieldbooks for the Sepphoris site excavations. These logs and notes were created by the area supervisors working for the dig team from approximately 1984 to 1997; includes the final site reports from 2000. Some of the fieldbooks exist at Duke only in digital form, as their hard copies are currently at the Hebrew University in Jerusalem. Other files represent physical copies in the collection. Some of these fieldbooks also contain Polaroid photographs that were affixed to the page of the book.
  - Object Shots by Sean Burrus, 2011-2015; 5 Megabytes 95 files (91 .jpg, 3 OLE2, 1 .DS-store) (Digital-materials UA.29.02.0027-SET-0001)
    These scans derive from photographs taken in 2011 by Sean Burrus (former Duke graduate student) for his chapter on the small objects discovered at Sepphoris III. There are four sub-folders by material (bone, ceramic, metal, and stone) and the file names contain the artifact registration number. The catalog numbers for the objects, which appear in Sepphoris III, are different than the registration number.
- Accession UA2019.0076, 1
  - Khirbet Shema, 1.1
    - Pottery drawings (Box 30)
      5 folders, packets
    - Balk drawings (Box 30)
      1 folder
    - Object drawings (ceramic, bone, stone, ivory, ostraca, misc.) (Box 30)
    - Lamp-fragment drawings (Box 30)
    - Drawings of metal objects (Box 30)
    - Drawings of glass fragments, vessels (Box 30)
      1 packet
    - Drawings of architectural fragments (Box 30)
    - Black and white photographs (Box 30)
      13 folders
    - Photographic negatives (Box 30)
    - 35mm slides (Box 30)
      1 3-ring binder
    - Newsclippings (Box 30)
    - Field books (Box 30)
      6 field books
    - Tomb 17 = miqveh, 1972 (Box 30)
    - Tomb 4 & Tomb Survey (1970); Tombs 29N, 30, & 31, 1971 (Box 30)
    - Tomb 29S (Box 30)
    - Miscellaneous tomb data, 1970 (Box 30)
    - Tomb Mausoleum (T. M.), 1970 (Box 30)
    - Manual for Area Supervisors (JSP), 1972 (Box 30)
    - Packets of pottery drawings (Box 31)
  - Gush Ḥalav, 1977-1978; 1.2
    - Pottery drawings, object drawings, 1977-1978 (Box 31)
    - Pottery drawings, object drawings, 1977-1978 (Box 32)
    - 35mm slides of Gush Ḥalav, 1977-1978 (Box 36)
      Small box; goes with 3-ring binder of Gush Ḥalav slides in Box 8 or Box 29.
  - Survey of Galilee and Golan, 1973; 1.3
    - Pottery drawings, gathered from unexcavated sites explored on foot, 1973 (Box 32)
  - Nabratein, 1980-1981; 1.4
    - Administrative matters, 1980-1981 (Box 32)
      4 file folders
    - Newsclippings, 1980-1981 (Box 32)
      2 large folders with flap and cord
    - Pottery plates (A-VV) (plus Sepphoris plates 1-36), 1980-1981 (Box 32)
      1 disc
    - 35mm slides, 1980-1981 (Box 36)
      Plastic box; goes with 3-ring binders in Box 12 or Box 13.
  - Meiron, 1971-1977; 1.5
    - Photos, 1971-1977 (Box 33)
    - Pottery drawings, 1971-1977 (Box 33)
      8 folders
    - Pottery drawings, MV, 1971-1977 (Box 33)
    - Pottery drawings, MIII, 1971-1977 (Box 33)
    - Pottery drawings, MIII, 1971-1977 (Box 34)
    - Pottery drawings, MI, 1971-1977 (Box 35)
    - Pottery drawings, MI, 1971-1977 (Box 36)
    - Slides of MII, MIII, objects, candids, 1971-1977 (Box 36)
      Box of slides, goes with other binders in previous accessions
    - Coin profiles, 1971-1977 (Box 36)
    - Object drawings––metal, glass, lamps & lamp fragments, misc. other objects, 1971-1977 (Box 36)
      4 folders
    - Drawings, plans, including architectural fragments, 1971-1977 (Box 36)
    - Negatives for pottery plates; descriptions by plate number, 1971-1977 (Box 36)
    - Pottery description sheets, 1971-1977 (Box 36)
    - 35 mm slides: overviews, drawings, Tomb 1 (T-1), Cisterns 1, 6 (C-1, C-6), MI.1–8[4] (Box 37)
      3-ring binder
    - Photos (Box 37)
  - Sepphoris, 1.6
    - JSP 75.1, 1985 (Box 37)
    - JSP 76.1, 1985 (Box 37)
    - JSP 84.1, 1985 (Box 37)
    - JSP 84.1, 1986 (Box 37)
    - JSP 84.1, 1988 (Box 37)
    - JSP 84.1, 1989 (Box 38)
    - JSP 84.2, 1985 (Box 38)
    - JSP 84.2, 1986 (Box 38)
    - JSP 84.4, 1989 (Box 38)
    - JSP 85.1: Hebrew University Report, 1980s (Box 38)
    - JSP 85.1, 1985 (Box 38)
    - SRP 84.1, 1993 (Box 38)
    - SRP 84.1, 1994 (Box 39)
    - SRP 84.4, 1993 (Box 39)
    - SRP 85.1, 1993 (Box 39)
    - SRP 85.1, 1994 (Box 39)
    - SRP 84.5, 1994 (Box 39)
    - SRP 84.5, 84.6, 1996 (Box 39)
    - SRP 85.1, 1996 (Box 40)
    - SRP 85.3, 1993 (Box 40)
    - SRP 85.3, 1994 (Box 40)
    - SRP 85.3, 1995-1996 (Box 40)
    - SRP 85.3, 1996 (Box 40)
    - SRP 85.3, 1997 (Box 41)
    - SAE 85.3, 2000 (Box 41)
    - SAE 95.1: A, B, C, 2000 (Box 41)
    - SAE 95.1: D, E, F, 2000 (Box 41)
    - SAE 95.2, 2000 (Box 41)
    - JSP 95.1, 1985 (Box 41)
    - JSP 85-89: Final Reports; Partial IN lists, 1986, 1985-1989 (Box 41)
    - SRP Final Reports; 1993 objects, 1993-1997 (Box 42)
    - SRP 84.1, 84.2, 84,4, 94.1, 95.1, 2011 (Box 42)
    - Anna Iamim's Reports (Box 42)